So in January of 2023, I was sexually assaulted and that experience revealed a lot to me about
myself and even more about the incapacity of those around me to support me through this horrific
experience. And so this year, as we come to the close of Sexual Assault Month here in the United
States, I've decided to release the unreleased chapter from my memoir, Body Waving Through
the BS, Crank That Through a Sexual Assault. This chapter speaks not only to my experience,
it speaks to the ways in which I got through it and as a guide to helping all of us be better at
showing up for everyone who has experienced this. Art has been an incredibly important aspect to my
healing. And I hope that for all of us who have experienced this, we are finding pathways to our
healing that we can stick to, that we can grow with, and that others are helping to fortify.
You can get Body Waving Through the BS, Crank That Through an Essay at amandalenexports.com.
Making my way away, Body Waving Through the BS.